Well, today's night comp idol is going to be a talk about the many charms of Akimoto-san.
I'm feeling a bit like a doofus,
Are you okay with that?
Please talk about it.
I was looking forward to it.
It's Akimoto-san, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
Akimoto-san is the center of our group,
She's our center, so she's the most flamboyant.
Oh, wow.
So you are the MC for important occasions and so on,
When you go out in front of the audience, Akimoto-san often takes the lead,
I think that helps me a lot,
I think that is something you can understand if you watch the show,
So I would like to talk about some of your great points that people don't know about you.
So I would like to show you something that people don't know about Akimoto-san.
What's your great point?
It's also my favorite part.
My favorite part.
I like her, and I wanted to tell you about her great points,
Yes, I do.
I think Akimoto-san is a very dominant person.
It's a little bit difficult to use this word.
This word is difficult. You may think, "Wait a minute,
First of all, he is a very strong man.
You seem to be physically strong, don't you?
Yes, I ran a full marathon the other day, last year? The year before last?
He ran a full marathon for the first time last year, or maybe the year before, and completed it in about 4 hours,
I heard that was an amazing feat.
That's an amazing record for a first time runner. It was my first time to set such a record.
And it wasn't that long ago that I decided to run a full marathon,
About six months ago, on the second day and a half before?
It was a sudden decision, and I didn't even know it,
I ran a lot, all over the city.
I was impressed,
I was thinking, "Wow, you must be really good.
And, you know, I had the most..,
The physical fitness episode that gave me goosebumps.
What is it?
I was really bullying myself,
I used to bully myself a lot.
Then, we went to a sauna together.
Hmph, hmph, hmph, hmph.
We went to the sauna together,
I think we went to a hot spring and there was a sauna.
I wasn't used to saunas at that time,
Akimoto-san seems to like saunas because he likes warm places,
But in a sauna, you just sit there and wait,
But in a sauna, you have to wait patiently and watch TV on a monitor or something,
I think the image of a sauna is that you wait and watch TV on a monitor and sweat slowly and steadily,
But Akimoto-san, in the sauna, he does muscle training,
But Akimoto-san does muscle training in the sauna.
Isn't that amazing?
And what's more, he doesn't do it as soon as he enters the sauna,
He doesn't do it as soon as he enters the sauna.
I'm not even warmed up yet,
I can move if I want to.
The hardest part of the day is the work, It's the hardest part,
I started to warm up and start sweating,
and you start to sweat, and you start to feel
I'm just starting to sweat,
Phew!
I started to get a little bit nervous. I was so surprised.
At that time, I was surprised and thought, "Akimoto-san has really gone this far.
It was as expected, there was no one around.
That's right. It was really a private party, just me and Honoka,
It seemed like they were choosing when to open the sauna for muscle training,
It was like they were choosing the right time to do muscle training, but they were doing muscle training in the sauna,
I was a bit of a fitness freak,
I thought he was a fitness nut, and that he likes to push himself hard,
I think that's an impression I don't get from other people,
I don't think that's an impression that many people have, but it's one of my favorite things about her,
Whenever I go out to the countryside with the members,
Whenever I go to the countryside with the members, we go to a big bath or a hot spring when we have time,
Whenever I have time, I go to a big bath or a hot spring with the members, and I always expect to see a sauna there.
Which muscle training is today?
I always do muscle training.
Well, it's also because it's so quick!
You can sweat right away.
No, that's right.
I'm not sure why you're so stoic about it.
I'm usually pretty easygoing and go at my own pace.
I never thought I'd be doing muscle training in a sauna.
I was a little surprised.
But I've heard Akimoto-san said he had a great time at the sauna with Sakura-san.
Wow, you know such an episode? Oh, my God, you know that episode?
Yes, where is it?
Well, we went to a sauna somewhere and Sakura and I danced to Lacio's "Bibibibi Bibi Girl" in the sauna.
Sakura and I danced to Lashio's "Bibi Bibi Shoujo" in the sauna.
That was fun, wasn't it?
Yes, it was. I witnessed Akimoto-san doing muscle training in the sauna,
I was able to get rid of the stereotype that it was okay to move in the sauna.
So I decided that if the sauna was reserved for a private party, I could move around as long as I didn't bother others,
At that time, it was just before we covered BiBi Bishoujo,
We danced as hard as we could in the sauna.
So we danced as hard as we could in the sauna.
You were watching Haru from the outdoor bath, right?
That's right. Mr. Sakamoto was watching from the outdoor bath,
He could see us dancing in the window, and he was dancing to our rhythm,
Mr. Sakamoto was dancing outside with us to the rhythm of our dancing.
Yes, it was almost a private party.
It was late in the day, and that college place.
So it was glass, glass, glass,
And there was Haru, and we were dancing,
Spring was there, and they were dancing.
They were dancing silhouettes.
That was fun.
That happened once.
It was a wonderful episode. Thank you.
Akimoto-san's personality.
Um, I only have DREAM left,
Is it physical?
But I think it's physical,
I think it will help me in my lessons,
I think it will be used in the lessons as well,I think it will be used in lessons and so on,
It is a part of respect, isn't it?
I have received a lot of respect from you.
So, I had a good time today.
We were able to talk about many things,
I was able to talk with you about many things, and I learned a new aspect of you.
Thank you very much.
I love you, Lo!
See you soon!